Okay, let's start today's live broadcast.
Today, the content of our live broadcast is a jacket with a special function.
In this live broadcast, I will show you how to make such a jacket from a basic sample.
In the course, I will show you how to make such a jacket from a modified to a made one.
The material will be sent to you in the official account later.
Don't worry.
Let's start today's content.
First of all, let's download a virtual model.
This class is a men's outfit.
OK, then we will import the template.
You can see that this template is a very simple plug-and-play.
If there is a user with such a template, you don't need it.
You can find a template.
You don't need to give it to the teacher.
Then, we move the template.
And then we size the template.
And then select the back piece and scale it.
Next, we arrange the template.
Select the front piece and arrange it in the front position.
And this side is a big template.
So we need to use a ruler to make it wider.
Then we choose the back piece and arrange it at the back
The same is to make the shoulder part a little bigger
Next, we use the sewing tool to sew it up
This is a relatively simple one, we sew it up quickly
Then there are two ropes here, we sew this rope up
After sewing, we can see that it is a jacket with such an insert sleeve
If the sleeve is here, let's sew it up, I forgot it just now
We can see that this jacket does not have a collar and a bottom
Next, let's make its collar
We use the editor tool to choose a circle of our collar
Then measure its length to 281.9
We use the sniper tool
We find the sniper tool
Then make a width of 281
Then a height that can be set to 160 mm
Then we do a match to open the editor
Then this is a straight version, very simple
Because I want to make a very high collar
So just sew it up from the back to the front
Let's take a look
Sew it up like this
Then we arrange the collar behind the neck of the model
So this is the thickness that we want to adjust
at this point
From the middle of the back to the middle of the front, sew it to the middle of the front, and then arrange this panel again.
You can see that this panel is relatively short, but it doesn't matter because it is a patterned panel.
After we use the patterned fabric, it will open it.
Next, we apply it and simulate it.
You can see that we have a shape of a coat.
Next, we use the zipper tool to add the front from the front to the bottom.
Double click
We can do it.
In this way, we have a basic version of a coat.
We apply this fabric to it.
Then we find the patterned fabric in our library.
We use this 2x2 gray pattern to drag it in and apply it to the bottom.
OK
Here, we can see that the patterned fabric is opened a little bit.
If you don't want it to be opened so much, we can choose the top of the patterned fabric and add a curve.
The proportion of the curve is set to 100.
The proportion is set to 100.
In this way, it is not stretched.
You can see it.
Next, let's take a look.
If I find some reference pictures like this, we will definitely make some emotional versions during the design process.
Then we can find some points that we need to refer to in our reference picture to design.
You can see that we basically sound in this kind of down jacket style.
Our new model is in our Connect mall.
You can download it from the mall.
OK
We can see that we are going to make a down jacket style here.
Next, we need to make an internal line border in the front of the bottom.
Here, we create a border for it.
Change it a little bit.
140mm wide border.
And then the sleeves here.
We are also.
And then the back piece.
Add some of these internal lines to it.
Click to confirm.
You can see.
In this way.
We added some of these airlines on the board.
In fact, the previous content is relatively simple.
It's all about how our style is made into a down jacket.
You can see.
Then the collar here.
We also add an airline in the middle of the two collars.
After we add all the boards to it.
We select the boards other than the pattern.
Then give it a colon layer inside.
After the colon layer inside.
We can wait a minute.
OK
Next, we add a pressure to the colon layer.
Then the inner layer.
It must be called a negative pressure.
Then we add a negative 20 here.
Then the outer layer.
We add a positive pressure to it.
We start the simulation.
In this way.
Our clothing.
Due to the pressure.
It will be held up.
Then here.
We change the pressure again.
Change it to negative 30.
Let it be a little bit more pressure.
It's a little bit full.
OK
Then we can take a look.
Here.
It is a design point that I mainly refer to in this course.
It has a division from the front to the sleeve.
Then there are some design like this.
We want to integrate this design into our clothing.
Then we can take a look.
How to make it out of it through the version.
First of all.
Use the inner line tool in the front.
Draw a inner line like this.
You can see.
I drew a line from the bottom to the sleeve.
Then.
Over there is the position of the sleeve to the sleeve.
Then you can see.
I drew these two lines.
What should you pay attention to?
That is.
You are in the position of the sleeve and the sleeve.
These two lines must be connected together.
Connected together.
Why?
Because.
If you don't connect them together.
Wait a minute.
If we do this.
He's sorry.
It doesn't look good.
You have to pay attention to this.
OK.
Let's give him the inner layer of this pattern.
Then he has a double layer.
OK.
What's next?
Let's take a look.
Because I need to be in.
I draw the inner line area.
Give him two panels.
These two panels.
Need to have a certain.
This.
That.
The number of points and the amount of compression in it.
Well.
We as designers.
Sometimes.
Do not know how to calculate the number of points.
Then we can use a simple method.
That is.
Let's just sew it up.
Two panels.
In this position.
Then pull the panels up.
At the same time.
It will return to the stage due to the function of the sewing line.
Then you will have the number of points and the compression.
Sometimes.
You will find that.
Like this.
This position.
If I say.
If I want to draw it out.
Then.
For example.
This place has a number.
I want to put these two panels.
There is a problem.
Then I have a way to use it.
The way is that we choose directly.
Then we will cut off the outer layer of the dragon.
After cutting off the outer layer of the dragon,
we will first remove the outer layer of the dragon.
Then we will cut it off from the line of the drawing.
In this way, we don't need to hook the board.
We just need to cut it off,
and we can get the same board hooked from the big body.
Then we delete the inner line in the middle.
We also need to delete the sewing line.
We need to pay attention to this point.
Because our shrinkage is mainly on the two sides of the board.
In fact, there is no shrinkage on the upper and lower sides.
So the whole extension is the two vertical lines.
We need to pay attention to this point when we sew.
Why do we delete the sewing line on the board of the dragon?
Because the board of the dragon is sewn in a circle.
If we stretch it like this,
it will have a shrinkage all day long.
Then we only need the shrinkage on both sides.
Then we just sew it on both sides.
On both sides.
Then we sew it on both sides.
When we stretch the board,
there is no shrinkage on the upper and lower sides.
There is only a shrinkage on both sides.
OK.
You can see that the board is directly in place.
It's very simple.
Then we need to stretch the board.
Let's count it first.
If you stretch it,
you will find that if I stretch it with the adjustment board,
the upper and lower lines of this board will have a certain deformation.
Right?
Because when it is stretched as a whole,
it will have a little deformation.
At this time, we can use another method.
Use the edit board tool directly.
Just select the upper line.
While selecting,
press the Shift key to extend.
You will find that the shape of the upper and lower lines
will not change much.
Because we keep the shape of these two lines.
Extend it a little.
OK.
Here, you don't need to enter specific parameters.
You can stretch it with your own feeling first.
Then simulate it to see its effect.
OK.
Let's add it to the outside.
Then look at its shrinkage.
OK.
I feel that the sleeve of the sleeve is a little short.
I will extend it a little more.
A little less.
OK.
Next,
in order to prevent the board on our clothes
from being stretched by these two long boards,
we add a flexible line to this inner line.
The ratio of the flexible line is set to 100.
In this way,
it can prevent this line from being stretched.
It will maintain its length change.
At this time,
that is to say,
sometimes because the particle diameter of this board line is relatively large,
I can't see the amount of the fold.
You can lower its particle diameter a little bit in advance.
It doesn't have to be too large.
Let's lower it to 12 first to see the effect.
OK.
Then we also add a flexible line to the inner line twice.
Then it maintains its length.
Don't be stretched by these two boards.
OK.
Next,
we give it these two fabrics.
Adjust it a little bit.
Add a little bit.
Next,
we apply a fabric to these two boards.
OK.
Next,
we apply a fabric to these two boards.
Add a little bit.
Adjust it a little bit.
OK.
You can see that
because these two boards are relatively wide,
there is a little bit of a pocket in the middle.
We can give it a pocket in the middle.
Because we are designing now,
so we can try to add a inner line like this.
Then add a flexible line to this inner line.
Then,
it also has some wrinkles in the middle.
You can see that the pocket is not so big.
Ok, then we can make a double layer effect on this side
Just add one more layer
We can finally sew a drawstring here
It's like a drawstring pulled out of here
Ok, then because it's symmetrical on both sides
I'll just do it on one side
After that, I'll just copy it to match it
Ok, then we're going to adjust this zipper
I'm going to change the color of the zipper here
OK, then we're going to adjust this zipper here
Then we're going to change the texture
Then we're going to choose the zipper strap
And then change the color of the zipper here
And then we're going to change the zipper
Because the zipper is more basic in our library
Then I'm in the software
Just open a business of our connect on our picture account
And then find the option of this trim
And then we can pick here
For example
I can take a look first
I can hook up here for free
And then find some material to pull the head
OK
Then there is such a pull head here
I'll just download it
At the same time
I also saw some of these pull heads
After I downloaded it
Drag it directly to the pull chain
You can use it
And then change the material to change the color first
And then change the material
OK
And then?
We can see here
There are some other accessories in the mall
Then we can download it all
In the afternoon
We can keep it there for later use
Just click download and that's it
There's another one here
The shape of the pull head
OK
Next, we can see this style
It's around this segment line
It's a wide band effect like a circle
Then we can save this design point
Then let's see how to do it
We directly select the position where we just did the segment
Measure its length to 881
And then we're going to build a width of 881
And then?
The height is for example
First, set a small plate with a diameter of one centimeter
Then we can sew it all the way to one side of it
Let's add it to the outside
Take a look
OK
What about this board?
After we've done it
You can find a piece of fabric and use it
OK
What about me?
I've prepared a piece of this kind of leather material in advance
Let's reduce the particle depth first
Then you can see that this bag is a little narrow
We can select the edge of this board
Make it a little longer
A little wider
like this
This effect is OK
Then a little bit shorter
OK
And then?
We also directly control the ground
Just copy it over there and that's it
Just turn it over
Ok
What about the next?
Let's take a look at this pattern
Change it to a color
good
And then?
We can do the same design in the where the seam center is
It's very simple
We use the interval line tool
From this directly to the route of this provinceよね
Draw an inner line and measure the total length of the rope from the rope to the inner line
For example, the total length is 763
Then we draw a long strip with a width of 763
Then sew it on the middle of the sleeve
Then we can increase the thickness of the strip
Then we can extend the strip
The length of the strip is extended
Because of the tension of the sewing line
There will be some wrinkles on the top
The line is not so monotonous
Then we sew the two sides
Ok, you can see the decoration on the side of the sleeve
Then we just give it a control plus D and copy it to the other side
Because we can now align and copy the 3D window
Just do one side and then the other side
When it is copied, it will be aligned directly
Good
Next, let's take a look at some details to add to the costume
The style of this kind of functional clothing
It must be that it has a lot of such pockets on the clothes
Let's take a look at some references
For example, like this vest
It has some such pocket shapes in front of the chest
Like this kind of clothing style
There will be some such three-dimensional pockets
Let's take a look at how to make such a three-dimensional pocket in colo
First of all, we can use the internal g-shaped tool
To create an internal g-shape on our costume
You don't need to care about its width and height
Then we first put it in place
Then see if it is suitable for the proportion of this costume
When it's ok
We can see that this side is a little small
Let's make it a little bigger
Make it a little wider
When the confirmation is complete
Let's start making this pocket
I'll make it a little wider on this side of the zipper
I'll make the internal g-shape of this drawing
Just make it Kekel as a plate
After the Kekeling plate
We sew it on the top of the costume
As the bottom of our pocket
Next, let's make the side of the pocket
This is very simple
Let's measure the entire square
Its length is 625
Then, let's use the g-shape tool
We will use this tool to create a length of 625
Then we create a height of 625
For width, we can make it 45
Then we use the sewing tool to sew the whole circle together with the board
Then add it to the side
Then we sew the opening
After sewing, you can see that the angle of the board is not too good
Then we can set the folding angle of the long strip and the square board
Then I can change the angle of the sewing line to 90
You can see that there is no change
Then I will change it back
Then I will add it again
For example, change it to 270
That is the opposite direction
That is 270 degrees
Let's take a look
Let's turn it a little bit
You can see that the angle of the sewing line is set
The volume of the three-dimensional part is raised
Next, we add a pinch to the side
Let it be a little bit harder
Then we copy the bottom part
The part that is copied is sewn together with the other side of the side
You can see that we give it a position first
OK
After sewing, it is also adjusted for it
First simulate
Then we adjust its folding angle
In general, if we make this kind of right-angle pocket
Its folding angle is not 90, but 270
well
OK
Of course, there are actually many ways to make pockets
Then we can demonstrate this kind of one-piece pocket
One-piece pocket making method
OK
Next, we will make a small pocket on this pocket
Bag in bag
OK
We also draw an internal shape on it first
Here, don't think about how much this size is
How big I want to draw
Then you draw it first
Then we look at the size to adjust
Don't bother about its size first
Then adjust its position
Then clone it as a plate
OK
We move this plate to its outline
This pocket
Then we only do one layer
We just measure its circumference
Then we directly use the curve tool to draw a
A long strip with a height of 452 and a width of 35
Then sew it up
You can see that I sew it together on both sides
Then right-click to add to the side
Let's simulate it for him
OK
Then this side is a little wider
We shrink the whole plate a little bit
A little narrower
Then this side is also added to him
After sewing
Let's adjust its folding angle with the edge sewing line tool
The folding angle here is also adjusted to 270
270 can be seen here
He bent inwards
So this angle is wrong
Then we just adjust it to another direction
90 degrees
You can see that he folded out
This side
Because of our current version of the particle diameter is relatively large
So he has a piece of the lower left corner here
Let's draw a line for him
Try to fold it
It seems that the effect is not very obvious
Let's just
Set an angle
Just delete it
Then my side is a little bit
Turn around a little bit under the state of simulation
Because the grid is folded in
Just pull it out
In this way
You can see that we have such a double-layer pocket
It's done
The method is very simple
Just draw a few pieces
Just sew them up like a goldfish
Then we
Let's make the particle diameter of this pocket a little bit smaller
To a 15
Then we can do some decorations on this pocket
For example, let's add a zipper for him first
Let's draw a zipper for him first
A position of opening
What about this zipper?
I set the width to 12
What about the length?
You can adjust it according to your own design
Then I
According to the position placed in the 2D window
Check the length of the zipper of this 3D window
Is it appropriate
This place
The long strip here just now
It's okay to sew it back
Let's put this pocket on the left side
OK
Wait a minute
Put it on the left side
Then after the next one is confirmed
Let's put this pocket
Turn over is not OK
Let's delete the bottom bottom layer of the sewing line
Then sew it to the left side
Then put the pocket down
Sewed together with our big body
Oh, put it back here
Well
Let's sew it again
I sewed it wrong just now
In this way, we can see that the opening of the pocket is on the left side of the whole pocket.
In terms of functionality, it is more convenient to open the zipper and take things like this.
Then we make the zipper strip a little shorter and then copy the zipper strip to the small pocket on the side.
You can see that the length on both sides is not the same.
Let's adjust it a little bit.
And then we convert the width of the two lines to be moved.
When you are doing this, you must pay attention to the width of the zipper.
You have to set the opening of the zipper in advance.
Although the length is set at random, the width is set in advance.
This is 12 mm, so pay attention to it.
Then we convert it to a move.
Then use the zipper strip directly.
You have to increase the width of the zipper, then increase the length of the zipper.
If you want to increase it by 3D, you can use the 2D plus.
Then you can see that I just know that the total width of my zipper is 12, so I add the zipper.
Then you can change the width of the zipper to 12.
And then on the other side.
This pocket looks like it is a little...
This pocket is sewn backwards.
I'll turn this plate over.
Turn it over to the front.
Turn it over on the side.
You can see that the seam is reversed here, and I will turn it over to the other side and sew it up.
Since we just turned it over to the other side, the seam line here cannot be changed according to the previous 270 degrees.
So let's change it to 90 degrees.
The zipper is a little bit too tight.
Since its diameter is 20, we can choose the zipper and change its diameter to 10.
Next, we will change the color of the zipper, the color of the zipper head, the color of the zipper, and the color of the belt.
For the zipper head, I will directly download and use it from the connection resource.
Since I have downloaded a batch just now, I don't need to be in this store.
I just open my backpack and find my folder.
You can see that this is the zipper I just downloaded.
I'll just apply it and rotate it.
Yes, we did it from the beginning.
If you listen to it from the beginning,
OK.
Then we add a decorative piece on the outside of this bag.
It will have some magic stickers or web cloths, etc.
We also put it in the same way.
Cut a piece of paper and sew it back.
Add it to the outside.
Then in the middle, we can draw a cross-sectional line.
Then sew it together with the inner line.
There is a feeling of sewing.
OK.
What about this side?
This decorative piece uses a different fabric.
I have a magic sticker on this side.
You can see it.
I prepared a reverse side of this magic sticker.
If we have some functional clothing like this,
you can stick some magic stickers on it.
So I made such a design here.
OK.
Then I draw a small one on it.
This place is small.
We can sew some logos or stickers later.
Something like this.
This is also a whole piece.
Sew it up.
OK.
Then I sew it together with the inner line.
Make a seam.
For example, I set a width of 1 mm for it.
Then reverse it.
The inside is the same.
Then sew it up.
OK.
You can see that our pocket is very close to the state of a real clothing pocket.
Then I add another small one on it.
This town has wood.
Add a jewel.
Then you made a degree.
Then I do a decorations.
You are interested in decorations.
The teacher's home can be spice.
See, you said,
you can use our magic tool.
The supporting tool is to make a small plate.
Then you can add a thing in the middle of this small plate.
Then I'll just admit this plate to our pockets.
Then because we just added a internal line like this in the middle
I'm going to use the folding arrangement tool
Fold the whole logo over in the 3D window
Fold it over
You can see that I folded it like this in advance
After folding
Let's take the particle diameter of this label
Because it's smaller
I can take it down to five first
Take it down to five
And then we'll just do the simulation
I changed the fabric for him
You have to move to this place
We can just right click on the label
Right click on this panel
There's a panel called Move to Sealed
And then you can see that it's already sealed
And then we'll simulate it
You can see that this label is sewn up
And it's in a state of folding
It's a relatively simple method
That's what we're doing before we simulate it
Draw a line for him first
And then fold it up
This angle
All right
And then we'll do this side
We can make it a little bit longer
Shorten it a little bit
The internal line in the middle can be deleted
Just as an auxiliary function
All right
And then we're going to take this one
Oh, I'm going to copy it out
And then we're going to add one to the bottom layer
And then we're going to take this pocket
The whole set of control plus D
Let's copy it to a symmetrical position
Because we have this pocket on both sides
Let's copy it over
We don't have any external accessories in our pocket yet
All right
After copying it
Let's move it a little bit
OK
And then what about this side
We only need one layer in our pocket
We can delete the second layer
Just keep one layer
All right
And then we're going to add a zipper
And then we're going to copy it to a symmetrical position
OK
Let's modify the zipper here
Some previews
The material, the color, etc.
All right
And then we're going to do this new layer
I'm going to make him a decoration like this on the outside
I'm going to cut him out
And then I'm going to sew this board up
What about this layer
I'm going to make him a mesh material
What about this side
He has some of this
You can see that here
We have some of these bands
What about this band
He can do something similar to storage functions
In our pocket
For example, you can put a pen in the middle
Or there are some tools
You can put it in
This kind of feeling
You should have seen this kind of decoration
Let's do this for him first
I'm going to use a mesh on this layer
And then sew it on
Draw a cross first
Same as on the left
All right
After sewing
Let's see how to make this kind of decoration
This kind of functional decoration bag
We can all take a look at it together
First of all
We use the internal line tool to draw a section of the internal line
What about the length
I set it to 20
All right
Set it to 20
There is no point to confirm
One more
Confirm
And then the double-click is over
After I get this line
I need to be in the middle
Give him an average of a few copies
How do we copy it
Select this line directly
Control C plus control V
You're in control V at the same time
Right click
You can pop up a sticky dialogue box
What about this
Any position in the shell is OK
That is, you copy it at the same time
Right click
You can pop up this sticky dialogue box
You can enter a number of you
It will be copied in the same order
It's not going to be copied one by one
Let's just wait for it to be copied
Four and then we click confirm
After confirmation
Let's do this row
Because I need to do three to four rows of lines like this
What about the rest of me
I just select this row of lines
And then?
Control C
Plus control V
At the same time
Right click
And then he's going to pop up a sticky dialogue box
You can see
I'm just going to copy the first row of lines like this
Four rows are very simple
And then?
Let's select this whole thing again
Move it around
All right
You can see that
So that we can sew it later
Because we don't have this dot on the side line
Wait a minute
We sew this
It might not be very convenient when we're in the middle of it
So we can use the straight line point tool in advance
Add a point to it
So we have this line on this board
When we were just at home
It's all random
So how do we determine the location of this point
This is very simple
We just use the plus point tool
On the edge of the board
You can see our line
This point
He will directly have a reference to the red one
No red line
He will absorb the nearest point and keep it even
That's what we're doing on the board
It's very convenient
You don't have to go
A little bit of positioning
Is this point right
Then we directly rely on its subtraction function
You can find the exact position parallel to this line
You can see that I'm adding this very quickly
Because he has this he has this auxiliary line
In fact, he can be like a magnet
Can be subtracted
I just want to add it quickly
Then we add it here
We're going to start making him a belt in the middle
We're going to use a straight board
Draw a long strip
What about this width?
That's the height
Just set it up for him
It's 20
It's the same as our internal line
What about the width
Let's set a 300 first
And then it's a little bit long
Shorten it a little bit
After shortening it a little bit
We can see that we need some internal lines in the middle
Sew it up
You can see how I did this place with patience
I just choose the two sides of the board
Line and then?
Right click to create an internal line between the lines
And then?
For example, I'll give him a grade of five
You can see that he's straight up
After that
I'm going to use the sewing tool
You can just cut it like this
Just sew it up
That's what we just added
A good point
You can see that he's going to sew it directly
You don't need us to go a little bit to aim at him
And then?
What about this side?
I'm going to apply a belt material to him
And then change the color
Click to confirm
OK
What about this side?
We'll give him in advance
It's a little bit bigger
Let's redo it
I'm going to change the color first
Let's redo the position of the second D
OK
Let's just simulate it
You can see that he sewed it up like this
And then I'm going to reduce his particle diameter
What about this side?
It's down to ten
It's down to five
It's a little bit smaller
You can see that this is what I want to do
It's like we can put some pens in the middle
Or some
Such a tool
Bala bala
We can shorten it a little bit
A little bit longer
OK
And then?
What about us next?
It's just the following few
You need to sew it up
We just need to copy it out
Control C and Control V to copy out
Okay
And then after we copy it
We're going to use the sewing tool to sew them all up
So the two parts have to be right here
To make sure every one of them is the same
And then what we're going to do
We're going to cut them at the end
We're going to go ahead and trim them
And then?
We're going to change it up
Next, we can make a decoration on the back of the front bag.
Remember, this is a decoration.
The same method.
First, we untie this plate.
Then, we make a large internal shape in the middle.
If you don't understand what I just said, you can take a closer look at this part.
Let's set its width.
Then, let's make it wider.
Then, let's cut it out.
Cut out a plate and sew it directly.
I extend the small plate a little bit.
Then, I only sew the inner circle.
In our clothing, there is a feeling of stitching.
There are some edges on the side.
It's not completely sewn, but there is a little seam left.
This is the feeling.
We can't use this fabric in this place.
Let's change it.
Then, let's use a fur-stained fabric here.
Next, draw an internal line like this.
Set the width and length to 35.
Then, we directly copy it from the first line.
Then, right-click and copy it out.
Then, click OK.
There are six numbers here.
Then, we move it to a good position.
Then, select this row directly.
Ctrl-C and Ctrl-V.
Then, click right-click and paste it at the same time.
Then, we can enter and copy a few rows.
It's very simple.
You can see that we can get a line like this quickly.
Basically, I only did one operation.
Basically, what's left is to copy and copy and copy.
Then, after making this line,
Let's just check it here.
I drew a total of seven lines.
Then, let's draw a long strip.
The width and height must be determined.
It's 35.
Then, the width can be set at will.
Then, in the middle of the two lines,
Give it a evenly divided into seven internal lines.
Then, click OK.
Then, we can sew it.
Before sewing,
We're going to add a dot here.
You can see that when we add a dot,
It has a brown line that can be diluted to the edge of this version.
It will give you a supporting line based on your recent points.
This line is very useful.
Yes, you can see it like this.
You see, I don't need to measure it.
Because it's parallel.
Yes, and then we sew it up.
It's okay.
Yes, the teacher is very skilled.
I'm so skilled that I can do it in my head.
I'm busy making clothes for a coke.
Okay, and then we sew it up.
After that, arrange it like this.
Turn it around and put it behind the clothing.
Then simulate it.
And then we're done.
Then we're done.
Then simulate it.
Okay.
It's a little too high here.
Let's shorten it a little bit.
Let's change the particle diameter first.
It's a little long.
Shorten it a little bit.
Okay, and then we copy it out like this.
There are five in total.
Then we'll give him five points.
That's the size of the pattern.
He's still learning.
I can't help you.
I'm away.
You can't stop.
No, you can't.
I'm sorry, there's no way you could.
Okay.
Let's give him a shot.
Okay, let's go.
I'll give it to you.
I don't want you to die.
I can't watch it.
If you go back up.
Please.
You mean, really?
You're going to take me, right?
Yeah, right.
I'll give you five points.
All right, let's go.
All right.
I'll give him a shot.
I'll give you five points.
Okay.
All right.
Then I'm going to give it a shot.
Ok, now we are done with the decoration of the back side.
Next, let's go to the front side.
We are going to make something similar to a tactical belt.
Let's take a look at the pendant.
On the pendant, there will be such a bow, such a日字扣, and the decoration of the insert button.
We are going to make something similar to an insert button or a日字扣.
Let's see how to make it.
First, I drew a board with the help of a tool.
You can see that I drew a board with the help of a tool.
I measured the width of the board.
Then I drew an inner line in the middle of this part.
Then I drew another inner line.
There are two inner lines.
This inner line is very simple.
We draw this inner line.
First, fold the first inner line in the middle with the folding tool.
Then we sew the edge and the second inner line together.
You can see that there are two seams here.
Then I copy another line from the front.
Why do I copy another line?
Because I want to sew a double layer like this.
Then the top of this small board is sewn together with the bottom of our pocket.
Let's change the size first.
Let's copy and paste it.
Then we copy and paste it.
You can see that here we made a side with an insert and an exit like this.
Then we need to do it on both sides.
We put an insert in the middle.
Then how do we do it?
We copy this small component directly.
Because its two sides are symmetrical.
We just press Ctrl to make this place a little longer.
Yes.
If you pull it a little longer, you can see that it is in the middle.
Because it is in the middle.
You can see that it is in the middle.
The position is shorter here and longer here.
So after it is folded, the amount here will be larger.
The amount here will be smaller.
You can see that it will naturally form such a arch like this.
Then we put the insert in the middle.
It's very simple.
Then we adjust the position of the seam.
Then we copy this panel out.
Then just rotate it around the latch.
Good point.
Now we copy two panels.
What do we need to do?
We need it in the middle.
I'll take the bottom one long.
I'll draw another little panel.
The width is the same as the width of our button.
Then apply a new fabric to it.
Then we go to the middle of this part,
The middle of the fold is the middle of the fold and the middle of the fold is the middle of the fold.
Okay, let's simulate it.
In this way, there is a space in the middle, right?
Then we can put the sunflowers in later and paste them on this small white board.
Then here, I want to tell you a little bit about the details.
If you do it directly like this, it may be a little bit messy when you stick the plug in the back.
Then what should we do?
You can drag your folding line in.
You can see that from the position of the folding line, I copied another one.
For example,
this is its folding line, right?
We copied another one from this base to it.
In this way, we put this board together with the line inside it.
You can see that in this way, the amount on both sides can be a part of the flash.
It's a little bit flat.
In this way, I put this white board in its pre-painted material.
Change it to a hard clay sticky.
In this way, the fabric will be a little bit harder.
After we stick the plug in the back,
if we change this board to transparent,
it will look like this from the front.
It will look like a day button connecting its two sides.
These are all business secrets.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll shorten the top a little bit.
OK.
I put it into the design of the box.
Keep in mind,
you need to make it as simple as a pattern.
It makes little patterns.
For example,
It is like drawing an artificial cube in the center.
Like making a small decoration like this.
Let me take a look
The method of this small discoveries
It's the same as the way of
And then we also give it the equal to generate some of these internal lines
And then we just sew it up on both sides
What we're going to do is very simple. It's all about drawing rectangle, square, rectangle, square
You see, there's not a single curve
All right, let's add it to the outside
Okay, and this is where it's actually a decorative thing turkey s ahora está aquí
Okay, so then we're going to cut it off a little bit down the left and right and then we're just going to bronzio and then we copy it to the left
And thereafter, when we come back to the left side, we don't need to be the same as the right side, so we unconnect it
Oh, and then we're going to delete the rest of the knock
Oh, this side, we'll give it one more time
You can see that I made this buckle a little narrower, and then I sewed two pairs of them under his pocket.
Like this, it's similar to what we can do with this little buckle.
You can add some, for example, such a lock buckle or a key buckle.
You can hang some of these things.
It's still a little functional in there.
OK.
Now, we're going to put the zipper in front of our chest.
We're going to add a few more sockets.
So we're going to take this set of accessories that we just made.
It's not this accessory, it's this bag.
I'll copy it out and move it to the front of our panel.
Let's take a look.
Then we can pull it a little wider at the edge of this panel.
It's symmetrical.
Let's take a look at the second line.
And then what we're going to do next is we're going to sew this buckle together with our clothing.
Let's take a look.
Let's put it in its place first.
How do we sew it in the middle?
We're going to go straight to the middle.
We're going to draw a internal curve for him.
Because he's square.
It's a little bit more solid.
We're going to draw a little bit narrower internal curve for him.
And then we're going to copy this curve directly to our big body.
You can see it's very simple.
We sew it up in a circle.
A model like this.
Then you can see that he's sewn up.
We don't need to position it at all.
Because he's a evaporation.
And then we're going to shorten the middle amount a little bit.
In this case,
We're going to make this buckle a group.
We can copy it out.
Three groups.
Okay,
And then we copy out another one.
Good.
So you can see him in front of his chest.
This is the location of the insertion in front of the chest.
We made it out.
And then?
Well, next thing we're going to do, we're going to make our.
Let's import our package into it.
The position of the front pocket is a little low.
Let's move it all the way up.
Let's save it and then delete this virtual model first.
Let's delete the model first.
Then import the package we prepared directly into the whole file.
We choose to add models and costumes.
In this way, we can import all the inside packages of the male package.
You can see it.
When you import it,
let's move the clothes down a little bit.
Then let's change the layer of the inner package to layer-1.
Then select the jacket and change the layer of the jacket to layer-1.
Then we can print the model.
OK
When the model is stable,
we can delete the layer of the clothes directly.
The zipper is a little unstable.
Just connect the layers.
Then modify it again.
Then unzip.
You can see it.
In this way, we can import the inner package of the inner package.
Delete the head cover.
I still feel that my hair looks better.
Then add the hair back to it.
So that the hair looks more natural.
Heel hair back is this.
We can see that the hair back is now straight.
This is a little bit difficult.
We're in this area.
It's a little bit of a challenge.
We can insert a layer of hair.
This is the hair back of the waistband.
This is a little bit difficult.
So we can insert another layer of hair.
We can insert another layer of hair.
Then I'm getting glasses.
So we can see that we have a lot of hair left.
This is our head hair now.
We can modify it.
It just have to be a little bit fragile.
Then we cut it this way.
And then we tie it in the pattern.
If you don't have this pattern.
You can use this pattern.
This is the reference.
You can see that this is the style.
I want to add it to the top.
Okay.
After we have finished drawing it,
we sew it around the outer corner of the face.
You can see that when I draw a symmetrical sheet, I draw half of it and then make it symmetrical, because in this case, when I sew it, I only need to sew half of it, because the two sides are linked.
OK, then we can put these X-Code components in it, put them in and add them.
First of all, we add it as a copy and then click OK, and then paste it on the white board in front of it, and then adjust its position and size.
You can see that because the volume of the two sides has been made, so you just need to place it.
But if it's too long, we can change its position and length by adjusting the model size of this 3D.
OK, you can see that this is basically a 3D model from the front.
This is the feeling of wearing in the middle.
Adjust the position a little bit more.
Then we adjust its material and its color to confirm it.
In this case, we copy the other side as well.
This side is also copied and adjusted to a good position.
After that, we also add this X-Code to it, and then import it to add a copy.
This version will not be shared.
I will only share the basic version to everyone.
You can change it yourself.
OK, let's change the color here.
When these OBJ models are imported, there is such a lock here.
We hang this bracket on its left side.
Take a look.
Because I downloaded two brackets at that time.
After we hang this one, let's take a look at the other one.
Which one is better?
Then after hanging this side, we will import this one.
The path is still in our public number.
The path is in B station.
I said it wrong.
Update in B station next week.
Then we hang this bracket in this position.
You are wrong.
Adjust it a little bit.
Then adjust the weight a little bit.
After hanging it, we can change this version from transparency to 0.
You can see that this X-Code is very real.
Put it here.
Then we will import some other components for it.
For example, such a lock.
Yes, the metal bracket is downloaded from the commercial city of Connect.
You can go to the commercial city and have a look.
Then adjust its material.
Color.
This one uses metal directly.
OK.
Then there are some places on the pants.
Then we can put this day button.
Also make some decorations for it.
Put it here.
OK.
Then here.
Add a key code for it.
The teacher uses Hui Pu.
2060.
Super.
Then here.
There is a key strap.
Let's hang it.
The models of these brackets.
Then I will share the basic version and this model with you.
If there are students who do it later,
You can practice.
If you want to use the same model,
You can go to the official website of our Connect.
You can download it from the official website.
You can use 1050 to cover the instant noodles.
Yeah.
Ok, now we have all the accessories and the brackets.
Let's copy some of them.
When we are doing the simulation, we are using a CPU to do the simulation, so it depends on the performance of your CPU.
You can't just look at the graphics card and your memory.
OK, next, let's change the position.
After the position is changed, the position will change.
Let's adjust it a little bit.
Yes, I'm walking on the road and staring at the light.
You can go to the shrapnel.
OK, let's simulate the last image.
Let's make it a little bit flat.
Add a lot of colors and hang them on the body.
Then let's make the decoration of the shrapnel a little bit lower.
OK.
Let's match it.
The simulation has nothing to do with the speed of the network.
How do you map to the speed of the network?
The simulation is related to the speed of the network.
We can ride the light video.
You will be very fast.
Then we will add some of the lines to it.
It's too fast.
Just like this.
Let's add some name lines as decoration lines.
I'll quickly add them here.
OK, let's do it.
Yes, the first two are pockets.
This student didn't look at the front.
The second one is here.
This type of clothing is suitable for private rooms.
It can hide a lot of clothes.
Yes, after we import the component, it will be simulated with the component's form.
Simulate with it.
We don't need to add the name line here, just add it.
You can add it later when you make it yourself.
You can also hang the car on it.
OK, let's see some final adjustments.
Here I have prepared a small logo.
Let's paste the logo on it.
OK, let's add a name line here.
OK.
OK, then we can go to the simulation window to simulate it a little bit.
You can see that the effect of our entire simulation window is still good.
And then I also prepared such a movement here.
OK.
Let's use the water pot and add this water pot to it.
You can see that there is such a small water pot here.
Very small.
Let's make it a little bigger.
Give it a 50.
120.
Make it a little bigger.
In this case, it won't be thirsty if it walks a long way.
When it is thirsty, it can bring its own water.
What a good man to go out and bring his own water pot.
Then let's adjust the material of this water pot.
The part of the lid on it, let's use a black one for it.
Then use a metal color for the flat position.
OK.
Where is the high-end logo of Cologne?
The high-end logo of Cologne is what the teacher wants in the company.
OK.
In this way, we have such a tactical jacket with such a skill.
It's done.
well
Our live broadcast of this issue is over.
Then see you next time.
Bye bye.